A Guide to the Louise Wright Bailey Genealogical Collection
Roanoke Public Libraries
- (Box 1)
  - Family Group Sheets (Box 6 of 12)
    - Turner, Tyree, Umbarger, Underwood, Updike, Van Der Burchgraeff (Folder 5)
    - Van Driel, Van Dusen, Vance, Vanderhoof, Varner, Varney, Vass (Folder 6)
    - Vaughn (Folder 7)
    - Vaught (Folder 8)
    - Vaught – Given names ‘A’ to ‘E’ (Folder 9)
    - Vaught – Given names ‘F’ to ‘I’ (Folder 10)
    - Vaught – Given names ‘J’ to ‘M’ (Folder 11)
    - Vaught – Given names ‘N’ to ‘W’ (Folder 12)
    - Vaught – Related families (Folder 13)
    - Vawter, Vencell (Vincell), Vermillion, Vest, Via, Vickers, Viers, Villamagne (Folder 14)
    - Vines, Vry, Waddel(l), Wade, Wagoner (Wagner), Walderson (Folder 15)
    - Walker (Folder 16)
    - Wallace, Wall(s), Waller, Walters, Walton (Walten), Ward, Warren (Folder 17)
    - Watkins (Folder 18)
    - Watson, Watts, Weatherford, Webb, Weis, Wellman, Wells, West, Weston, Wheeler (Folder 19)
    - White (Folder 20)
    - Whitescarver, Whitlock, Whitt (Folder 21)
    - Whittaker (Folder 22)
    - Wickline, Wieciech, Wiggins, Wildasin, Wiles (Folder 23)
    - Wilburn (Wilbourn(e), Wilborn, Wellborn) (Folder 24)
    - Wiley (Folder 25)
    - Williams (Folder 26)
    - Willis, Wills (Wells), Wilson, Wimmer, Winegar, Winfrey (Folder 27)
    - Winston, Wirtz, Wise, Wiseman, Wit, Withrow, Witten, Woodworth (Folder 28)
    - Wohlford, Wolf(e), Wood(s), Woodall, Woodram, Woodyard, Woolford, Woolwine (Folder 29)
    - Workman, Worley, Wright (Folder 30)
    - Wright Connections – Abegglin to Austin (Folder 31)
    - Wright Connections – Baber to Booth (Folder 32)
    - Wright Connections – Bourne to Byrd (Folder 33)
    - Wright Connections – Callahan to Cline (Folder 34)
    - Wright Connections – Coburn to Cutchshaw (Folder 35)
    - Wright Connections – Dahlen to Dykes (Folder 36)
    - Wright Connections – Eads to Ewing (Folder 37)
    - Wright Connections – Falin to Funk (Folder 38)
    - Wright Connections – Gamble to Guthrie (Folder 39)
    - Wright Connections – Hackler to Hampton (Folder 40)
    - Wright Connections – Hancock to Hutton (Folder 41)
    - Wright Connections – Ingalls to Isom (Folder 42)
    - Wright Connections – Jackson to Jones (Folder 43)
    - Wright Connections – Kane to Kyle (Folder 44)
    - Wright Connections – Lamb to Lynn (Folder 45)
  - Family Group Sheets arranged alphabetically by surname (Folders 1-18). (Box 7 of 12)
    - Wright Connections – McAbster to McNew (Folder 1)
    - Wright Connections – Machele to Miller (Folder 2)
    - Wright Connections – Mills to Mustard (Folder 3)
    - Wright Connections – Nash to Nuckolls (Folder 4)
    - Wright Connections – Obediah to Owens (Folder 5)
    - Wright Connections – Painter to Pyrtle (Folder 6)
    - Wright Connections – Quicksal to Rutherford (Folder 7)
    - Wright Connections – Sage to Sprinkle (Folder 8)
    - Wright Connections – Slamey to Sword (Folder 9)
    - Wright Connections – Tackett to Tyson (Folder 10)
    - Wright Connections – Umbarger to Vaught (Folder 11)
    - Wright Connections – Waddle to Wyn (Folder 12)
    - Wright Connections – Yale to Ziggler (Folder 13)
    - Wright – Given names ‘A’ to ‘I’ (Folder 14)
    - Wright – Given names ‘J’ to ‘W’ (Folder 15)
    - Wriston (Folder 16)
    - Wyatt (Folder 17)
    - Wyckoff, Wygol (Wygle), Wynn, Wyrick, Wysong, Wysor, Yates, Yocum, Yost, Young (Folder 18)
    - Index of Marriages for Straley Husbands (Folder 19)
    - Index of Marriages for Straley Wives (Folder 20)
    - Source list for Bailey research (Folder 21)
  - Folders 22-46 contain indexes of courthouse records arranged alphabetically by geographical location (Box 7 of 12)
    - Arkansas: Clark County (Folder 22)
    - Kentucky (Folder 23)
    - Tennessee: Blount County (Folder 24)
    - Virginia: Augusta County (Folder 25)
    - Virginia: Bland County (Folder 26)
    - Virginia: Botetourt County (Folder 27)
    - Virginia: Bristol (Folder 28)
    - Virginia: Culpeper County (Folder 29)
    - Virginia: Franklin County (Folder 30)
    - Virginia: Frederick County (Folder 31)
    - Virginia: Giles County (Folder 32)
    - Virginia: Grayson County (Folder 33)
    - Virginia: Montgomery County (Folder 34)
    - Virginia: Prince Edward County (Folder 35)
    - Virginia: Roanoke (Folder 36)
    - Virginia: Roanoke County (Folder 37)
    - Virginia: Rockbridge County (Folder 38)
    - Virginia: Rockingham County (Folder 39)
    - Virginia: Russell County (Folder 40)
    - Virginia: Shenandoah County (Folder 41)
    - Virginia: Smyth County (Folder 42)
    - Virginia: Warren County (Folder 43)
    - Virginia: Washington County (Folder 44)
    - Virginia: Wythe County (Folder 45)
    - West Virginia: Mercer County (Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous – Diary of Judith Bailey, detailing trip to England, 16 to 30 April 1986 (Folder 47)
    - News Clippings – Miscellaneous (Folder 48)
    - News Clippings – Rhudy Family (Folder 49)
  - Folders 50-68 contain Mrs. Bailey’s research notes, arranged alphabetically by surname (Box 7 of 12)
    - Allen (Folder 50)
    - Anderson (Folder 51)
    - Bailey (Folder 52)
    - Bailey – Unchecked sources (Folder 53)
    - Bevin (Bevan) (Folder 54)
    - Bigg(s) (Folder 55)
    - Booker (Folder 56)
    - Boren (Folder 57)
    - Boyer (Folder 58)
    - Browne (Folder 59)
    - Bryan (Folder 60)
    - Button (Folder 61)
    - Canterbury – Unchecked sources (Folder 62)
    - Carr (Folder 63)
    - Chapman (Folder 64)
    - Chiles (Folder 65)
    - Clay (Folder 66)
    - Clay Family Quarterly, Volumes 1-7 (Folder 67)
    - Clay Family Quarterly, Volumes 8 and 9 (Folder 68)
  - Bailey research notes, arranged alphabetically by surname. (Box 8 of 12)
    - Clay Family Quarterly, Volume 10 (Folder 1)
    - Clay Family Quarterly, Volumes 11-14 (Folder 2)
    - Clay Family Quarterly, unidentified (Folder 3)
    - Clay – Unchecked sources (Folder 4)
    - Cock (Koch) (Folder 5)
    - Cook(e) – Unchecked sources (Folder 6)
    - Cornett – folder 1 of 2 (Folder 7)
    - Cornett – folder 2 of 2 (Folder 8)
    - Creagar (Folder 9)
    - Cresap (Folder 10)
    - Dabney (Folder 11)
    - Dancey (Folder 12)
    - Darnall (Folder 13)
    - Davis (Folder 14)
    - Dickins - Unchecked sources (Folder 15)
    - Emmons (Folder 16)
    - Eppes (Folder 17)
    - European ancestral connections - surnames ‘A’ to ‘G’ (Folder 18)
    - European ancestral connections – surnames ‘H’ to ‘O’ (Folder 19)
    - European ancestral connections – surnames ‘P’ to ‘Z’ (Folder 20)
    - European ancestral connections – miscellaneous (Folder 21)
    - Farley connections with unidentified surnames (Folder 22)
    - Farley, French, Wilburn, 6 January 1984 (Folder 23)
    - Farley – Unchecked sources (Folder 24)
    - Fleming (Folder 25)
    - Fontaine (Folder 26)
    - Forbis (Forbush) (Folder 27)
    - French – folder 1 of 2 (Folder 28)
    - French – folder 2 of 2 (Folder 29)
    - Garland (Folder 30)
    - Gilly (Folder 31)
    - Gose (Folder 32)
    - Gould (Folder 33)
    - Gunno(e) (Folder 34)
    - Guthrey (Folder 35)
    - Hail (Folder 36)
    - Hand (Folder 37)
    - Harbour (Folder 38)
    - Hardbarger (Folder 39)
    - Hendrick(s) - Unchecked sources (Folder 40)
    - Hophmire (Folder 41)
    - Hord (Folder 42)
    - Horsley (Folder 43)
    - Hughes (Folder 44)
    - Jennett (Gennet) (Folder 45)
    - Johnston - Unchecked sources (Folder 46)
    - Jordan (Folder 47)
    - Kettering (Folder 48)
    - Knutsen (Folder 49)
    - Layton (Folder 50)
    - Long (Folder 51)
    - Lupo (Folder 52)
    - Lynch (Folder 53)
    - Lynn (Folder 54)
    - McComas – Unchecked sources (Folder 55)
    - McCraw (Folder 56)
    - McGraw, Francis (Folder 57)
    - Maddox (Folder 58)
    - Mayo (Folder 59)
    - Mees (Folder 60)
    - Merritt (Folder 61)
    - Morgan (Folder 62)
    - Murphy (Folder 63)
    - Norwood (Folder 64)
    - Norsworthy (Folder 65)
    - Nugent (Folder 66)
    - Oliphant (Folder 67)
    - Page (Folder 68)
    - Patton (Folder 69)
    - Payne (Folder 70)
    - Perrat (Folder 71)
    - Peters - Unchecked sources (Folder 72)
    - Phillippie (Folder 73)
    - Purefoy (Folder 74)
    - Rair (Folder 75)
    - Ransome (Folder 76)
    - Remine (Romine) – folder 1 of 2 (Folder 77)
    - Remine (Romine) – folder 2 of 2 (Folder 78)
    - Remy (Folder 79)
    - Riffe – Unchecked sources (Folder 80)
    - Robinett (Folder 81)
    - Rhudy (Folder 82)
    - Settle (Folder 83)
    - Smith (Folder 84)
    - Sparrow (Folder 85)
  - Folders 1-28 contain Bailey research notes, arranged alphabetically by surname. (Box 9 of 12)
    - Stafford (Folder 1)
    - Steel (Folder 2)
    - Stillwell (Folder 3)
    - Stewart (Stuart) (Folder 4)
    - Stewart – Unchecked sources (Folder 5)
    - Straley (Folder 6)
    - Straley-Vaught, 24 March 1984 (Folder 7)
    - Sutherland (Folder 8)
    - Surface (Folder 9)
    - Tabb (Folder 10)
    - Thompson (Folder 11)
    - Tinker (Folder 12)
    - Trout (Folder 13)
    - Tyler (Folder 14)
    - Vaught (Folder 15)
    - Vines (Folder 16)
    - Wallace (Folder 17)
    - Waller (Folder 18)
    - Watkins (Folder 19)
    - Waugh (Folder 20)
    - West (Folder 21)
    - White (Folder 22)
    - Wilburn (Folder 23)
    - Winston (Folder 24)
    - Woodhouse (Folder 25)
    - Woodson (Folder 26)
    - Wright (Folder 27)
    - Wyatt (Folder 28)
    - Obituaries (Folder 29)
    - Photographs: negatives – unidentified (Folder 30)
    - Photographs: McCraw Reunion, 1984 (Folder 31)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous (Folder 32)
      - Bob, David, Jan and Ken Smork, 1998 (Item 1)
      - Unidentified family, unknown date (Item 2)
      - Harry Bailey and unidentified women (Item 3)
      - McCraw Family Reunion, group photo, Mt. Airy, NC, 1992 (Item 4)
      - 8 photos of an unidentified structure, unknown date (Item 5)
    - Publications – Clay Family Quarterly, index of first names (Folder 33)
    - Publications – Clay Family Quarterly, Volume 1 to 2:3 (Folder 34)
    - Publications – Clay Family Quarterly, Volume 2:4 to 6 (Folder 35)
    - Publications – Clay Family Quarterly, Volume 7 to 8 (Folder 36)
    - Publications – “Genealogical Gleanings in England” (Folder 37)
    - Publications – “Genealogical Tables of European Royals” (Folder 38)
    - Publications – “Hardesty’s West Virginia Counties: Kanawha County”, excerpt (Folder 39)
    - Publications – “A History of Monroe County, West Virginia”, excerpt (Folder 40)
    - Publications – “A History of Summers County, West Virginia”, excerpt (Folder 41)
    - Publications – Jefferson High School, Class of 1947 reunion program (Folder 42)
    - Publications – “Journals of the House of Burgesses”, excerpts (Folder 43)
    - Publications – “Marriages of Monroe County, West Virginia, 1853-1900” (Folder 44)
    - Publications – “Old World Progenitors of the Wyckoff Family” (Folder 45)
    - Publications – Orkneyinga Saga: “Genealogy of the Earls of Orkney” (Folder 46)
    - Publications – Reference Book of Wyoming County History, excerpt (Folder 47)
    - Publications – Seedbed of the Republic: “List of Tithables, 1772” (Folder 48)
    - Publications – “Twelve Generations of Farleys” (Folder 49)
    - Publications – Virginia Genealogist, Volume 6:1: “Dabney of King William County, Virginia” (Folder 50)
    - Publications – Virginia Genealogist, Volume 29:1: “Choctaws in Virginia in 1772” (Folder 51)
    - Publications – Virginia Genealogist, Volume 31:4: “Martha (Clay) Bass and her Daughter Mary (Bass) Clay of Henrico and Chesterfield Counties” (Folder 52)
    - Records – Marriages – Surnames Allen to Anderson (Folder 53)
    - Records – Marriages – Surnames Bailey to Burk (Folder 54)
    - Records – Marriages – Surnames Canterbury to Cock (Folder 55)
    - Records – Marriages – Surnames Dabney to Degges (Folder 56)
    - Records – Marriages – Surnames Fielden to Friel (Folder 57)
    - Records – Marriages – Surnames Garland to Guthrey (Folder 58)
    - Records – Marriages – Surnames Hale to Hall (Folder 59)
    - Records – Marriages – Jennett to Robinett (Folder 60)
    - Records – Marriages – Surnames Sparrow to Wycoff (Folder 61)
  - Folders 62-78 contain records arranged alphabetically by geographical location and type of record thereunder. Please note that census records listed during non-census years were generated from substitute census records, such as tithables and personal property tax records. (Box 9 of 12)
    - Alabama: Census, 1830-1850 (Folder 62)
    - Arkansas: Census, 1840-1880 (Folder 63)
    - Barbados: Parish Registers, undated (Folder 64)
    - California: Census, 1850 (Folder 65)
    - Colorado: Census, 1870-1900 (Folder 66)
    - Connecticut: Census, 1790 (Folder 67)
    - Dakota Territory: Census, 1860-1880 (Folder 68)
    - District of Columbia: Census, 1900 (Folder 69)
    - Florida: Census, 1850 (Folder 70)
    - Georgia: Census, 1820-1880 (Folder 71)
    - Illinois: Census, 1810-1850 (Folder 72)
    - Indiana: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 73)
    - Iowa: Census, 1840-1900 (Folder 74)
    - Kansas: Census, 1860 (Folder 75)
    - Kentucky: Miscellaneous records (Folder 76)
    - Kentucky: Adair to Knox County: Census, 1790-1900 (Folder 77)
    - Kentucky: Lawrence County: Marriages, 1822-1859 (Folder 78)
  - Records arranged alphabetically by geographical location and type of record thereunder. Please note that census records listed during non-census years were generated from substitute census records, such as tithables and personal property tax records. (Box 10 of 12)
    - Kentucky: Lawrence to Woodford County: Census, 1810-1880 (Folder 1)
    - Kentucky: Various counties: Marriages, 1794-1850 (Folder 2)
    - Louisiana: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 3)
    - Maryland: Census, 1790 and 1810 (Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts: Census, 1790 (Folder 5)
    - Minnesota: Census, 1850-1870 (Folder 6)
    - Mississippi: Census, 1850 (Folder 7)
    - Missouri: Census, 1830-1870 (Folder 8)
    - Montana: Census, 1870 (Folder 9)
    - Nebraska: Census, 1860-1870 (Folder 10)
    - New Hampshire: Census, 1880 and 1900 (Folder 11)
    - North Carolina – Military: Revolutionary records of Francis Gilley (Folder 12)
    - North Carolina – Military: Revolutionary records of Jacob Goss (Folder 13)
    - North Carolina – Military: Revolutionary records of Joshua Welborn (Willborn) (Folder 14)
    - North Carolina: Ashe County: Will of Samuel Song, 16 December 1842 (Folder 15)
    - North Carolina: Chowan County: Marriage application of Edward Fisher (sic) to Sarah Bare, 11 October 1779 (Folder 16)
    - North Carolina: Various counties: Census, 1790-1860 (Folder 17)
    - North Carolina: Various counties: miscellaneous (Folder 18)
    - Oklahoma: Cherokee Nation: Census, 1890 (Folder 19)
    - Ohio: Census, 1820-1860 (Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania: Baptism and marriage records of John C. Stoever, 1730-1779 (Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania: Census, 1790-1810 (Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania – Military: Revolutionary records of Jacob Rudy (Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania – Military: Revolutionary records of George Voght (Folder 24)
    - South Carolina: Miscellaneous (Folder 25)
    - Tennessee – Military: Confederate records of Lindley Remine (Folder 26)
    - Tennessee – Military: Revolutionary records of David Hughes (Folder 27)
    - Tennessee: Miscellaneous (Folder 28)
    - Tennessee: Anderson to Humphreys County: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 29)
    - Tennessee: Jackson to Warren County: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 30)
    - Texas: Census, 1850-1880 (Folder 31)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of William French (Folder 32)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of Richard Gilley (Folder 33)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of Richard Horsley (Folder 34)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of Matthew Maddox (Folder 35)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of Isaac Roman (Folder 36)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of John Romine (Folder 37)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of Alexander Sutherland (Folder 38)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of Thomas Vines (Folder 39)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary records of Richard Wright (Folder 40)
    - Virginia – Military: Revolutionary soldiers (Folder 41)
    - Virginia – Ministers Returns of William Forester, 1802-1842, Northern Neck (Folder 42)
    - Virginia – Patents granted, 1700-1736 (Folder 43)
    - Virginia – Pensions, Revolutionary War (Folder 44)
    - Virginia – Petitions, Bibliography, Calendars, Abstracts (Folder 45)
    - Virginia: Accomack to Augusta County: Census, various years (Folder 46)
    - Virginia: Albemarle County: Miscellaneous (Folder 47)
    - Virginia: Amelia County: Miscellaneous (Folder 48)
    - Virginia: Amherst County: Miscellaneous (Folder 49)
    - Virginia: Bedford County: Census, 1782-1850 (Folder 50)
    - Virginia: Bland County: Census, 1850 and 1870 (Folder 51)
    - Virginia: Bland County: Marriages, 1861-1929 (Folder 52)
    - Virginia: Botetourt County: Marriages, 1769-1800 (Folder 53)
    - Virginia: Botetourt County: Tithables, 1770, 1771 and 1800 (Folder 54)
    - Virginia: Botetourt to Buckingham County: Census, various years (Folder 55)
    - Virginia: Buckingham County: Tithables, 1773-1800 (Folder 56)
    - Virginia: Campbell County: Miscellaneous (Folder 57)
    - Virginia: Campbell to Cumberland County: Census, various years (Folder 58)
    - Virginia: Charles City County: Wills/Deeds, 1766-1774 (Folder 59)
    - Virginia: Chesterfield County: Miscellaneous (Folder 60)
    - Virginia: Craig County: Miscellaneous (Folder 61)
    - Virginia: Cumberland County: Marriages, 1749-1800, includes some post-1800 dates (Folder 62)
    - Virginia: Dinwiddie to Essex County: Census, various years (Folder 63)
    - Virginia: Fairfax County (Folder 64)
    - Virginia: Fairfax County: Indenture to George and Sarah Lamkin by Willoughby Tebbs, 18 March 1787 (Folder 65)
    - Virginia: Fairfax County: Indenture to Robert Sanford and Peter Dow, 12 January 1785 (Folder 66)
    - Virginia: Fairfax to Frederick County, Census, various years (Folder 67)
    - Virginia: Fauquier County: Marriages, 1759-1800 (Folder 68)
    - Virginia: Frederick County: Administrative bond of Margaret Wilburn, 2 December 1746 (Folder 69)
    - Virginia: Frederick County: Court Orders, 1748-1789 (Folder 70)
    - Virginia: Frederick County: Personal Property Tax Lists, 1782-1795 (Folder 71)
    - Virginia: Frederick County: Wills/Deeds, 1753-1809 (Folder 72)
    - Virginia: Giles County (Folder 73)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Births, 1855-1896 (Folder 74)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Census, 1840-1850 (Folder 75)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Census, 1860 (Folder 76)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Census, 1870 (Folder 77)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Census, 1880 (Folder 78)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Census, 1900 (Folder 79)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Deaths, 1871-1913 (Folder 80)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Marriages, 1871-1940 (Folder 81)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Personal Property Tax Lists, 1806-1849 (Folder 82)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Will of Matthew French, 23 June 1812 (Folder 83)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Will of Stephen Wilburn, 23 May 1843 (Folder 84)
    - Virginia: Giles County: Wills/Deeds. 1810-1936 (Folder 85)
    - Virginia: Gloucester County: Tax Lists, 1770-1782 (Folder 86)
    - Virginia: Gloucester to Goochland County: Census, various years (Folder 87)
    - Virginia: Grayson County (Folder 88)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Births, 1853-1860 (Folder 89)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Births, 1853-1860 (Folder 90)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Census, 1800-1850 (Folder 91)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Census, 1860-1870 (Folder 92)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Census, 1870 – Elk Creek District (Folder 93)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Census, 1880, 1900-1910 (Folder 94)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Deaths, 1853-1870 (Folder 95)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Deeds – Conveyance to J.M. Vaughan and L.J. Funk from George Wright, 6 March 1879 (Folder 96)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Marriages, 1793-1853 (Folder 97)
  - Records arranged alphabetically by geographical location and type of record thereunder. Please note that census records listed during non-census years were generated from substitute census records, such as tithables and personal property tax records. (Box 11 of 12)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Tax List, 1810 (Folder 1)
    - Virginia: Grayson County: Wills, 1795-1839 (Folder 2)
    - Virginia: Greensville to Henrico County: Census, various years (Folder 3)
    - Virginia: Hanover County: Miscellaneous (Folder 4)
    - Virginia: Henry County: Census, 1782, 1810-1850 (Folder 5)
    - Virginia: Henry County: Land Grants/Patents, 1779-1792 (Folder 6)
    - Virginia: Henry County: Tax List, 1810 (Folder 7)
    - Virginia: Henry County: Wills/Deeds, 1786-1805 (Folder 8)
    - Virginia: Isle of Wight to Mecklenburg County: Census, various years (Folder 9)
    - Virginia: King and Queen County: Miscellaneous (Folder 10)
    - Virginia: Lee County: Census, 1820-1850 (Folder 11)
    - Virginia: Loudoun County: Tithables, 1771 (Folder 12)
    - Virginia: Louisa County: Marriages, 1767-1800 (Folder 13)
    - Virginia: Lunenburg County: Marriages, 1763-1792 (Folder 14)
    - Virginia: Lunenburg County: Vestry Book of Cumberland Parish, 1746-1816 (Folder 15)
    - Virginia: Mathews County: Tax Lists, 1774, 1782 and 1791 (Folder 16)
    - Virginia: Montgomery County: Court Orders, 1773-1855 (Folder 17)
    - Virginia: Montgomery County: Marriages, 1757-1800 (Folder 18)
    - Virginia: Montgomery County: Personal Property Tax Lists, 1787-1800 (Folder 19)
    - Virginia: Montgomery County: Will of John Thompson, 22 February 1805 (Folder 20)
    - Virginia: Montgomery County: Wills/Deeds, 1704-1933 (Folder 21)
    - Virginia: Montgomery and Fincastle County: Marriages, 1773-1831 (Folder 22)
    - Virginia: Montgomery to Northampton County: Census, various years (Folder 23)
    - Virginia: New Kent County: Parish Registers, 1684-1786 (Folder 24)
    - Virginia: Northern Neck: Land Patents, 1749-1790 (Folder 25)
    - Virginia: Northampton County: Tithables, 1666 (Folder 26)
    - Virginia: Orange County: Miscellaneous (Folder 27)
    - Virginia: Orange County: Order Books, 1734-1745 (Folder 28)
    - Virginia: Patrick County: Census, 1790-1900 (Folder 29)
    - Virginia: Patrick County: Cemeteries (Folder 30)
    - Virginia: Patrick County: Tax List, 1821 (Folder 31)
    - Virginia: Petersburg to Powhatan County: Census, various years (Folder 32)
    - Virginia: Prince Edward County: Census, 1810-1850 (Folder 33)
    - Virginia: Prince Edward County: Marriages, 1754-1850 (Folder 34)
    - Virginia: Prince Edward County: Personal Property Tax Lists, 1810-1837 (Folder 35)
    - Virginia: Prince Edward County: Wills/Deeds, 1754-1915 (Folder 36)
    - Virginia: Prince George to Princess Anne County: Census, various years (Folder 37)
    - Virginia: Pulaski County: Births, 1855-1871 (Folder 38)
    - Virginia: Pulaski County: Census, 1850-1860 (Folder 39)
    - Virginia: Pulaski County: Deaths, 1862-1868 (Folder 40)
    - Virginia: Pulaski County: Marriages, 1839-1900 (Folder 41)
    - Virginia: Pulaski County: Military, 1861-1865 (Folder 42)
    - Virginia: Rappahannock to Rockingham County: Census, various years (Folder 43)
    - Virginia: Rockingham County: Marriages, 1795-1825 (Folder 44)
    - Virginia: Rockingham County: Peaked Mountain Church Records, 1745-1802 (Folder 45)
    - Virginia: Russell County (Folder 46)
    - Virginia: Russell County: Census, 1785-1860 (Folder 47)
    - Virginia: Russell County: Personal Property Tax Lists, 1820-1843 (Folder 48)
    - Virginia: Scott County: Census, 1814-1860 (Folder 49)
    - Virginia: Shenandoah County: Census, 1790-1850 (Folder 50)